OLGA CHERNEGA

Junior Front-End Developer



CONTACTS

+38 068-383-77-07

M Kyiv, Ukraine

elian-cheng

Oleandera#2061

SKILLS

• Web-development: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript

• Version control: Git, GitHub

• Editors: VS Code

• CMS: WordPress

• Photo editor: Adobe Photoshop

• Computer: Windows, MS Office

• Touch-typing: Russian, English and Chinese

LANGUAGES

English: Advanced

• Chinese: Proficient

• Russian: Advanced

• Ukrainian: Native

PROFILE

Creative person with rich life and work experience. Lived for 6 years in China, then moved back to Ukraine. Accustomed to work with international clients, excellent knowledge of English and Chinese. At first worked in logistics and product manufacturing. Then studied marketing for a long time, working in finances and sales.

Start of war in Ukraine gave me some free time to reconsider my life prospects and study something I wanted for a long time: IT development. So I'm successfully doing it for already 6 months with a significant progress and a portfolio full of new projects, you can see on my GitHub.

EXPERIENCE

 Best Income, Kyiv 2021.06-2022.07

client management, financial consulting and service sales

Business 4Smart, Kyiv (Ukraine)
2018.04-2021.06

client management, negotiations, consulting and service sales

 Color Trend LLC, Yiwu (China) 2014.06-2018.01

working in China, inspection and shipping, following manufacturing process, negotiations, client management

EDUCATION

 Lanzhou University, Lanzhou (China) 2012.09-2015.07

master degree: Chinese language and characters

 Interregional Academy of Personnel Management, Kyiv (Ukraine) 2012.06-2014.02

master degree: Administrative management

 Kyiv National University by Taras Shevchenko, Kyiv (Ukraine) 2008.09-2012.05

bachelor degree: Chinese language, literature and translation